AndreasKvistad

Computer Science Engineer Student

Personal

Andreas Henriksen Kvistad 23. September 1993 Fjellhamar

Contact

Singsakerbakken 4d, Apartment 22a 7030 Trondheim

+47 975 46 336

ahk9339@gmail.com fb://andreas.kvistad.9

Languages

Norwegian English fluency German beginner

Programming

♥ Python Java, C++ HTML

Myself

I am a 24 year old computer science engineer student with a specialization in artificial intelligence. I'm a fast learner, and I like being active in my spare time. I have played football since age six, and I'm currently playing for NTNUi. I chose computer science because I have always been interested in computers, and always enjoyed subjects like math and physics. I grasped programming quickly, as I found it both fun and challenging.

Education

2013–2018 Masters Degree Computer Science Engineer

Norwegian University of Science and

Technology, NTNU

Specialization in Artificial Intelligence

Five-year study of computer science, and a specialization in artificial intelligence after two years. Master thesis about deep learning for NLP, specifically for question answering systems and active learning.

2016–2017 **Exchange Student**

University of California, Santa Barbara

Full year abroad in California, Santa Barbara, on my fourth year of studies. Involved a lot of project works, and more social interaction between students and teachers because of the small class sizes.

Experience

Full Time

2012 – 2013 Benterud Skole (Primary School)

Benterud Skole, Lørenskog

Teaching Assistant, Daycare worker, Substitute Teacher

Worked at a primary school mainly as a teaching assistant for kids with difficulty in learning, or just helping the teacher out with smaller tasks. I sometimes substituted for teachers in different subjects. Finally, I also worked in the daycare for pupils up to the fourth grade.

Experiences:

- Being patient and creative whilst teaching others
- Promote good behaviour and generally being a good role model
- Being professional and honest when interacting with parents and teachers

Part Time

2010 - 2012 **Losby Gods**

Losby Gods, Lørenskog

Service Employee

Worked as a waiter in both bigger events as weddings and also á la carte in the restaurant. Involved a lot of interaction with customers and co-workers. Experiences:

- "The customers always right" Treating the customer in such a manner
- Working under a person in charge, respecting orders
- Still being able to smile after 12 hours at work

Summer Internships

2016 & 2017 Statnett SF

Oslo Nydalen

Summer Intern

Two-part job. Measured grounding in high-voltage tower-pylons, and their capability of leading potentially harmful current away from the tower and safely into the ground. The second part was to plan and draw grounding for new tower areas. This consisted of measuring the relative earth resistivity, and drawing sketches of the area the tower. We then added sufficient grounding to the drawings, according to the measurements we got, along with the general topography of the area. Most of the work were done on-site, on different high-voltage lines around the country.

Responsible for training another team the second year, joining them for a week and supervising their work.

Experiences:

- Working in a large-scale company under a leadership
- · Closely work in teams of two, most of the summer
- Carry out professional work which adhered to the standards of Statnett SF
- Plan day-to-day work, in order to meet the agenda set by Statnett SF

Interests

professional: Programming, artificial intelligence, deep learning, software development, computer graphics

personal: Football, guitar, exercise, music, computers

References

Statnett SF Arild Kvamme Berstad

Oslo, Nydalen

Certificate written by Arild Kvamme Berstad, Engineer at UTLE - Statnett SF, can be provided upon request.

Contact:

- +47 909 95 149
- arild.berstad@statnett.no

Benterud Lillian Lauritzen

Benterud Skole, Lørenskog

Person of reference, Lillian Lauritzen, Substitute Teacher Organizer Contact:

- +47 977 90 764
- lillau@lorenskog.kommune.no

Losby Gods Heidi Fjellheim

Losby Gods, Lørenskog

Person of reference, Heidi Fjellheim, Director Contact:

- +47 970 69 620
- h.fjellheim@losbygods.no